Thank you for watching!
Oh, no, I've got a bad feeling about this.
Come on, let's grow up.
I mean, I don't need anyone
I don't want it.
Oh, shit.
I can feel it in my feet.
Oh, God.
Can we go home?
You should try the Tokyo Tower.
Let's go.
Campagne.
You can't if I go.
Hi, I'm Tokyo Day. Please!
And Mr. Sakuma, please.
They are here today as well.
Funny, funny, funny! Everyone is funny!
Leave the comedy to us!
Seino, it's Ruff Ruff!
Please!
They're planning another location today.
Someone went on location. Who?
Yes! Sasaki Nagamatsu Natsume.
What kind of project did the three of you do together?
Well, Rika and Harurun mentioned singing at the last project presentation competition,
I had auditioned for a singing contest called Uta-chan, so the three of us went together for a karaoke project this time.
How did you respond? The location itself.
Ryoka was very funny and made us laugh.
I hope you can hear their wonderful singing voices. Please go ahead.
Wait a minute.
I don't know where to go with this. Just look at it anyway.
Okay, um, the scale is 30 percent.
That's unusual. I can see that on TV.
Even on TV, you don't get 30 minutes nowadays.
It's unheard of.This is unprecedented.
So this will be divided into two halves.
What? Half an hour from now?
If there is anything that bothers you, please stop.
If anything bothers you, please stop.
Good morning.
We're here today for Japanese karaoke, right?
I don't know.
I did call out to you, though.
Do you come to karaoke?
I come here often with my friends.
We came yesterday.
You came here yesterday?
Do you go here often?
I used to come here with my friends.
I don't go with friends.
I go with my sister.
It's scary going with your sister.
It's not as scary as the Gettys.
You want to jump?
The three of us had different roles to play.
It would have been better if we had decided who was going to be the facilitator
Karaoke project
It's also a director's problem
After-school talk among the three
That's not bad at all
Who will be the facilitator?
Who to do location work with
If there were three, who could do it?
If it was just the three of us, who could do it best?
I have to ask myself whether or not Nagamatsu is the best.
At this point, Nagamatsu is the one who will do it.
Yes, sir.
Go! Go!All right! Go!
Go! Go!
After-school talk for three.
You're early.
Where's your mom?
Where's your mother?
Where's Mom?
Hey, hey, hey.
Excuse me.
The lucky mom from the karaoke project.
It's got to be real.
What are you doing with who? It's so fake.
Like a fake.
Radio tower
Sounds like the Sky Tree.
I'm stuck here.
I want you to speak plainly.
What's he doing?
That 4x4.
I think I can take it from here.
Oh!
The first person to get a bingo gets to go home.
Wow!
Oh, my God!
Is that what I think it is?
But I don't get all the 90s and stuff.
Thirty-three?
80?
Wait a minute.
I can go home with at least four songs.
Oh, my God!
Can you do it?Can you do it?
Wow!
This is pretty hard to do, isn't it?
Drinks OK, no food.
What do you mean?
This is fine.
I want to eat.
I don't know.
I can't play bingo like that.
What's your highest score?
Ninety-eight.
That's great.
I got a 100 on Ashitama's song.
That's amazing!
What am I going to do?
I don't know.
Should we go this way?
I think I can make it back here.
If we hang in there, somehow we're gonna get out of here.
You're right. Wait.
A hundred points.
It's a toe ball.
Can you do it?
Yes, sir.
I see.
That's great.
It's a little high, isn't it?
Handwritten bingo karaoke!
This is important.
I'd like to open with Sasaki from the first shot.
I'll go with Sasaki and score 90 points.
I wonder if we'll make it.
I wonder if it will go 90
I'll meet you here at 90.
Camera.
I'll change, won't I?That's going to change.
That energy will always be there.
The camera.
A star is formed when a spark collides with a star.
A lonely star that can't stand in a constellation
But still, still, still, every time I hear it
It shines, it gets stronger, it lights up the night
I just love you, that's all that matters
And yet, my emotions are rushing through the fall
That's right, this love, this magic, is a starisk
A little love the size of the palm of your hand
Your smile seems so far away
I don't care if I can't reach you
A shooting star will take you away
To the far reaches of the galaxy, all alone...
Twenty-five.
Oh, wow.
That's good for the big one.
Next.
I can make GusGus's voice echo from now on.
Because I'm...
I'm not a girl.
I'm gonna miss you.
One more time.
Mm-hm.
Oh!
She's cute.
He's got a smile on his face, doesn't he?
You're spoiling him.
Not like old times.
I don't get anxious.
I'm feeling happy.
I can be kind
Even when it's so cold
When it's so cold that you hide from me
When your breath glows whiteWhen your breath glows white
I feel like Yururi
You're so excited
Look at that gesture
I can still see it on your face
The best days of my life
Dusk is the color of
The whistling of winter
I'll try to keep it warm
I'll keep you warm
Just the two of us
Can't we just go home?
I think we can all go home in four songs, right?
That's a 76 for today.
Well then...
I hope you all understand what I'm saying.
Thank you very much.
First of all, isn't the number of moves stupid?
Yes, it is.
Seventy-six points!
Yes, sir! Let's have fun!
Yes!
Thank you!
I am now...
I'm such a mute.
Nice! That's good!
I just spit it out.
A cloud called loneliness
That cloud
Let it rain
Filling up
I can't hold on to it anyway
My first kiss
I want it to happen again
Love bites me and says it won't let go
It says it won't let goYou say you won't let go
But the form of loneliness seems to be the same
So soar away
Someday on the other side of the night
Something for both of us
Hikaru Kimi no Uta
I saw a shooting star
I Saw a Shooting Star
My Song of Wishing
Thank you!
Come on, let's see if you got bingo.
That's cool.
Some of us don't have bingo.
Cool!
I mean, we're not even home yet.
Oh, shit!
No way!
Oh, no!
I got a 90!
I scored a 90.
70 doesn't happen very often.
I see.
Let's see how many points we can get next time.
On the other hand, if you hit it wrong, it's good.
But if I do, I'll go here.
Because it's 83.
You're right.
80 points is not so bad.
Then let's go for 92.
I'll get something... a 92.
It's gonna be tough.
That's what I'm trying to say.
This is gonna be fun.
What the hell was that?What the hell was that?
Yeah, I can do anything if it makes you laugh.
I'm a little bossy, but somehow I've got the courage
If I could make you happy again and again, like a flower falling and blooming
That's how I'll live my life... and that's why I want to be strong.
All right.
Yes, yes, yes.
Oh, that's good.
Oh!
You can go home now.
Hey, Gu.
Come here.
I'd like to leave in four songs.
Let's go
When the ozurikiru comes, time stops for the two of us
Furitsukiyo
Ahoy pen
Wonderful.
Hi.
We're the I-Awai kids.
Hey, hey, are you okay?
Oh, hey!
700 lucky!
I knew it! Patokin looks good!
It's true, Anmyo Chudo has never been so much fun!
I could feel the tension in the corners.
Yay!
I was in love.
Put your earphones away!
I'll see you later!
Wait!
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, you want to do that?
Yes.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
I think they're leaving, right?
Yeah!
Let's go home to life.
We're all going home, aren't we?
Yeah.
BGM
Oh, here we go.
BGM.
Why are you hiding your face?
BGM
That's a hard song to sing.
Softly, softly, softly embracing the brightness of things that have no form
I'm going forward
I want to go home.
Even now...
There's something I want you to hear.
I'd be happy if you smiled.
Happiness isn't like a starry night
It's not like a starry night and a dazzling morning.
That's why I want you by my side.
Thank you.
I'll give you a kiss for the feelings I've just realized
Because no words will ever be enough
I'll give you a kiss, I can't believe I like you now
I'll give you a kiss, it's just a little kiss
Your smile is like the sun
I'll give you a kiss, I'll give you a kiss, I'll give you a kiss
I want to look at you so badly I'd die
I want to be your hand
What are you going to do when you love me?What are you gonna do when you love me?
You're just gonna walk away
Hey, what do you want?
I can't promise you just one more time
Far, far away Metelgeuse that won't stop
I want to tell you the same thing
I feel like I can live on my own
Oh!
I can't go on and on.
Come on, come on, come on. It's time to eat.
I'm starving and you're not feeding me.
Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
You're alive all over again now.
Thank you for watching until the end.
Today's version is the crying version.
Sign me up!
We'll be waiting. No, please.
Please, please, please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please.
Please, please, please, please